# RICHARDKANG

HTML = CSS = JAVASCRIPT = REACT = REACT NATIVE = EXPRESS = RUBY = RAILS = NODEJS = POSTGRESQL = SEQUELIZE

Software engineer trained in full stack web development, studying various fields of visual arts, with 6+ years in employee development. Creativity being my driving passion allows me to both consistently produce unique works for clients while also thinking outside the box for general problem solving. Along with my love to create, encouraging growth and positivity in the workplace continue to be significant points in my journey, leading me to have organized numerous events for youth career growth programs, fundraisers, and job fairs.

(347) 639 - 8151
RICHARDKANGG@GMAIL.COM
NEW YORK CITY
WILLING TO RELOCATE

HTTP://RICHARDKANGG.COM
HTTP://LINKEDIN.COM/IN/RICHARDKANGG
HTTP://GITHUB.COM/RICHARDKANGG

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### PROFESSIONAL GENERAL ASSEMBLY, NEW YORK, NY

**EXPERIENCE** Software Engineering Fellow, October 2019 – January 2019

- Studied and continued to polish skills in various coding languages while tasked with developing full stack applications from scratch implementing front end, backend, database, and design.
- In a joint effort with UX designers, developed a cookbook website showcasing a collection of recipes based on what ingredients the user has in stock, using both third party and mock APIs, React, Javascript, HTML, and CSS.
- As a team, developed a music education app, paired with a virtual piano to store and play usercreated melodies, using React, Express, and Sequelize.
- Sole developer for a gardening simulator/game, allowing users to grow and maintain various plants while learning how to care for different types, using aforementioned languages along with Rails

### LG, MARKETSOURCE, JAMAICA, NY

Market Sales Manager, March 2018 - October 2019

- Oversaw all aspects of talent development and LG sales in Queens, responsible for recognizing product trends, monitoring performance, creating action plans to maximize business results in each location, providing counsel on areas of opportunity.
- Acted as support and leader for NYC region in absence of Regional Sales Manager.

#### **OLD NAVY, LONG ISLAND CITY, NY**

Senior Business Operations Manager, November 2015 – July 2017

- Promoted operational efficiencies and development of store team, tracking business performance and diagnosing how to amplify success, addressing opportunities that support or detract from profitability.
- Recruiting, hiring, training, and coaching brand associates, supervisors and managers to
  positively impact the store steam, the customer experience, and general store operations.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **GENERAL ASSEMBLY**, NEW YORK, NY Software Engineering Immersive 2019

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Experience in graphic design, photography, and film for both marketing and creative purposes, using tools including Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Premiere Pro